<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on sirwritealot</title>
    <link>https://sirwritealot.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on sirwritealot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:35:10 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sirwritealot.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elevator Escalation</title>
      <link>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:35:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/07/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Defender is the worst product ever,&amp;rdquo; Mansi said chomping down on her eggs.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;What?&amp;rdquo; She asked looking at the stunned faces in front of her.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Nothing. I was just saying that he worked in Defender before.&amp;rdquo; Mansi&amp;rsquo;s colleague said pointing towards his left. The person on the left had his hand frozen trying his best to smile.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Oh, I didn&amp;rsquo;t mean it that way. Windows defender is still better than Update software,&amp;rdquo; Mansi said in full damage control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster we fall</title>
      <link>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:33:46 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/06/</guid>
      <description>Mansi decided that she would kill him. Not because he threw water on her precious clothes; not because he teased to date her sister; and definitely not because he was cute. She decided that the only way everyone in the office would stop teasing her about him was if he didn&amp;rsquo;t exist. &amp;ldquo;I know it&amp;rsquo;s not the right thing but what choice do I have?&amp;rdquo; Mansi thought and mixed the juice with a little alcohol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder at First Sight</title>
      <link>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:31:25 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/05/</guid>
      <description>Mansi decided that she would kill him. Not because he threw water on her precious clothes; not because he teased to date her sister; and definitely not because he was cute. She decided that the only way everyone in the office would stop teasing her about him was if he didn&amp;rsquo;t exist. &amp;ldquo;I know it&amp;rsquo;s not the right thing but what choice do I have?&amp;rdquo; Mansi thought and mixed the juice with a little alcohol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rotten Parched Lips</title>
      <link>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:30:21 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/04/</guid>
      <description>Mansi touched her lips and was annoyed.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Damn these rotten parched lips.&amp;rdquo; She said and reached for her lip balm. As usual, it was just out of her reach. She stretched her arm and before she could balance her feet on the ground, the wheels of the chairs moved backwards and she was flying towards the ground.&#xA;She saved her face by placing her hand on the ground and heard a crunching sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disease Extrapolation</title>
      <link>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:28:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/03/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I think I have throat cancer,&amp;rdquo; said Mansi in a somber whisper.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;What?&amp;rdquo; Her friend asked choking on his innocent sip of water. You don&amp;rsquo;t have the watercooler talk to discuss matters of life or death. Mansi nodded, her expression fixed and her eyes shifty. Worry was visible on her face and was now mirrored on his.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;How?&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;You know I&amp;rsquo;ve been coughing for the past week. During my travel, I fell completely off the wagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pen or Sword</title>
      <link>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:27:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/02/</guid>
      <description>Mansi picked up a pen and used it like a sword. Not defying governments or changing the world order by writing the next masterpiece. She literally picked the pen and stabbed him with it. Her intention was clear. His leg should be the canvas for her.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Are you done?&amp;rdquo; He drawled and continued watching the movie. Then pen had failed her. She looked at the pen incredulously. She turned to her own hand and saw that the pen was working perfectly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prioritization Paradox</title>
      <link>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sirwritealot.com/clumsygirl/01/</guid>
      <description>Mansi wept!&#xA;She wanted to take a knife and slash at her computer. The stupid machine had decided that it was more important to restart right now than let her work. She called the machine names which would have brightened her mother&amp;rsquo;s ears and then cursed the company that made the operating system. All in her head as she worked for the company.&#xA;She had to run the script before 5:30 pm, otherwise, she won&amp;rsquo;t be able to go home till 7 pm.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
